Jan Karon papers MSS 16077
University of Virginia, Special Collections Dept.
- Professional correspondence and papers, Series III
  - Public Appearances and Author Events – Trinity Presbyterian Church, Montgomery, Alabama, “A Day in Mitford” an event planning guide, 1999 April 20; 1 folder(s) (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Public Appearances and Author Events (1 of 2 folders), 2001; 1 folder(s) (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Public Appearances and Author Events (2 of 2 folders), 2001; 1 folder(s) (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Public Appearances and Author Events - First National Book Festival, 2001; 1 folder(s) (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Public Appearances and Author Events, 2002; 1 folder(s) (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Public Appearances and Author Events – Albemarle County Historical Society Event at Esmont Farms, 2004 June 13; 1 folder(s) (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Public Appearances and Author Events – Carnegie Library Museum Opening Celebration, Perry, Iowa, 2004 September 25; 1 folder(s) (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Public Appearances and Author Events – First International Mitford Homecoming, Ridgecrest, North Carolina, 2005 June 24-26; 1 folder(s) (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Public Appearances and Author Events – Dallas Celebration of Reading, 2005 October 24; 1 folder(s) (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Public Appearances and Author Events – Washington National Cathedral Jan Karon lecture “Writing and Wrestling with the Heart”, 2005 December 6; 1 folder(s) (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Public Appearances and Author Events – Book Tour for "Light from Heaven", 2005; 1 folder(s) (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Public Appearances and Author Events – “Eleganza Benefit” for the Mariam and Robert Hayes Performing Arts Center, 2006 August 12; 1 folder(s) (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Public Appearances and Author Events – Bookmarks, Winston-Salem’s Festival of Books presents “A Conversation with Jan Karon”, 2006 November 7; 1 folder(s) (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Public Appearances and Author Events – Page and Palette Bookstore, Fairhope, Alabama, Violet cat drawing contest and play, 2006 November 8; 1 folder(s) (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Public Appearances and Author Events – Book Tour, 2006; 1 folder(s) (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Public Appearances and Author Events – Second International Mitford Homecoming, Blowing Rock, North Carolina (1 of 4 folders), 2007 September 12-16; 1 folder(s) (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Public Appearances and Author Events – Second International Mitford Homecoming, Blowing Rock, North Carolina (2 of 4 folders), 2007 September 12-16; 1 folder(s) (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Public Appearances and Author Events – Second International Mitford Homecoming, Blowing Rock, North Carolina (3 of 4 folders), 2007 September 12-16; 1 folder(s) (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Public Appearances and Author Events – Second International Mitford Homecoming, Blowing Rock, North Carolina (4 of 4 folders), 2007 September 12-16; 1 folder(s) (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Public Appearances and Author Events – Book Tour for "Home to Holly Springs", 2007; 1 folder(s) (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Public Appearances and Author Events, 2008; 1 folder(s) (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Public Appearances and Author Events, 2014-2015; 1 folder(s) (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Public Appearances and Author Events - Itineraries, 1994-1998; 1 folder(s) (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Public Appearances and Author Events - Itineraries, 2001-2014; 1 folder(s) (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Public Appearances and Author Events - Photographs, 1995-1996; 1 folder(s) (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Public Appearances and Author Events – Photographs, 1997; 1 folder(s) (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Public Appearances and Author Events – Photographs, circa 1996-1997; 1 folder(s) (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Public Appearances and Author Events – Photographs, 1998-2002; 1 folder(s) (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Publicity – Bestseller Lists, 1996-1997; 1 folder(s) (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Publicity – Bestseller Lists, 1998; 1 folder(s) (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Publicity – Bestseller Lists, 1999-2000; 1 folder(s) (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Publicity – Bestseller Lists, 2001-2002; 1 folder(s) (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Publicity – Catalogs, 1994-1995; 1 folder(s) (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Publicity – Catalogs, 1996; 1 folder(s) (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Publicity – Catalogs, 1997-2002; 1 folder(s) (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Publicity – Catalogs, 2003-2011; 1 folder(s) (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Publicity – Catalogs, inserts removed from catalogs including notecards, 2003-2012; 1 folder(s) (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Publicity – Catalogs - Large Print, 1996-1999; 1 folder(s) (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Publicity – Mitford Event Kit, 1998, 2000; 1 folder(s) (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Publicity- Posters and Maps of Mitford, (9 items oversize), 1994-2005; 1 folder(s) (Oversize folder flat file 17)
  - Publicity - Display Boards, [1997-2005]; 1 folder(s) (Oversize box 1, Oversizefolder 9)
  - Publicity – Posters promoting Jan Karon’s Mitford books, (7 oversize posters), [1996]-2003; 1 folder(s) (Oversize box 1, Oversizefolder 7)
  - Publicity – Posters promoting Jan Karon’s Mitford and children’s books, (11 oversize posters), 2006-2007, undated; 1 folder(s) (Oversize box 3, Oversizefolder 4)
  - Publicity – Press, 1994-1995; 1 folder(s) (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Publicity – Press, 1996; 1 folder(s) (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Publicity – Press, 1997 January-July; 1 folder(s) (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Publicity – Press, 1997 August-December; 1 folder(s) (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Publicity – Press, 1998; 1 folder(s) (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Publicity – Press, 1999 January-April; 1 folder(s) (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Publicity – Press, 1999 May-December; 1 folder(s) (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Publicity – Press, 2000-2002; 1 folder(s) (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Publicity – Press, 2003-2015; 1 folder(s) (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Publicity written by Jan Karon for her own work, 1995-[2001], 2015; 1 folder(s) (Box 56, Folder 7)
    Other examples of publicity written by Jan Karon can be found in the editorial correspondence associated with individual books in series one or the correspondence with publishers in this series.
  - Publicity – Floor Display Headers and Risers (oversize), 2001-2007; 1 folder(s) (Oversize box 3, Oversizefolder 5)
  - Publicity – Television Advertising Boards for "A Common Life" (oversize), [2001]; 1 folder(s) (Oversize box 3, Oversizefolder 6-A)
  - Publicity – Television Advertising Boards for "In This Mountain" (oversize), [2002]; 1 folder(s) (Oversize box 3, Oversizefolder 6-B)
  - Publicity – Television Advertising Boards for "The Mitford Bedside Companion" (oversize), [2006]; 1 folder(s) (Oversize box 3, Oversizefolder 7)
  - Requests for Public Appearances, 1996-1997 July; 1 folder(s) (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Requests for Public Appearances, 1997 August-December; 1 folder(s) (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Requests for Public Appearances, 1998 January-April; 1 folder(s) (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Requests for Public Appearances, 1998 May-June; 1 folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Requests for Public Appearances, 1998 July-September; 1 folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Requests for Public Appearances, 1998 October-December; 1 folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Requests for Public Appearances, 1999 January-April; 1 folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Requests for Public Appearances, 2001-2015; 1 folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Reviews, 1994-1996; 1 folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Reviews, 1997; 1 folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Reviews, 1998-2001; 1 folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Short Stories, 1992-1999; 1 folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Stationery and Business cards, while writing in Blowing Rock, North Carolina, undated; 1 folder(s) (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - "Victoria Magazine", 1997; 1 folder(s) (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - "Victoria Magazine", 1998-2000; 1 folder(s) (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - "Victoria Magazine" - Writer in Residence, 1998; 1 folder(s) (Box 58, Folder 4)
    Writer in Residence pieces by Jan Karon as published in the magazine; typed drafts are included in the two previous Victoria Magazine files, 1997-1998.
  - "Victoria Magazine" and "Tea Time" magazines, 2006-2008; 1 folder(s) (Box 58, Folder 5)
    File includes the article describing a white tea held by Jan Karon at her Esmont home in "Tea Time" and “A Room of Her Own” in "Victoria Magazine"
  - Viking-Penguin Editorial File, 1995; 1 folder(s) (Box 58, Folder 6)
    This correspondence documents the publishing career of Jan Karon with Viking-Penguin and reveals the level of her involvement in decisions about illustrations and covers, promotion, advertising, and a host of other details. They will be most useful used in conjunction with the editorial correspondence that accompanies most book files in series one.
  - Viking-Penguin Editorial File, 1996; 1 folder(s) (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Viking-Penguin Editorial File, 1997; 1 folder(s) (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Viking-Penguin Editorial File, 1998-1999; 1 folder(s) (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Viking-Penguin Editorial File, 2000-2001; 1 folder(s) (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Viking-Penguin Editorial File, 2002-2004; 1 folder(s) (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Viking-Penguin Editorial File, 2005-2007; 1 folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Viking-Penguin Editorial File, 2008-2015; 1 folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Viking-Penguin Editorial File - Book Jackets and Designs (oversize), circa 2002-2004; 1 folder(s) (Oversize box 1)
- Personal and Family Papers
  - Personal and Family correspondence
    - Clergy Correspondence, 1995-2002; 1 folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 3)
      Includes a sermon by Bishop Harvey, June 8, 2000.
    - Clergy Correspondence, 2003-2015; 1 folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Clergy Correspondence - Bishop Keith L. Ackerman and Jo Ackerman, 1997-2016; 1 folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Clergy Correspondence – The Reverend Gale H. Cooper, 1996-2007, 2014; 1 folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Clergy Correspondence – The Reverend Christopher Henderson, 2001; 1 folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Clergy Correspondence – The Reverend Christopher Henderson, 2002; 1 folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Clergy Correspondence – The Reverend Christopher Henderson, 2006-2015; 1 folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Clergy Correspondence – The Reverend Bruce McMillan, rector of Christ Church, Holly Springs, Mississippi, 2006-2007; 1 folder(s) (Box 60, Folder 1)
      Includes a sermon by him; McMillan assisted Jan Karon with questions about information used in Home to Holly Springs.
    - Clergy Correspondence – The Reverend Bruce McMillan, rector of Christ Church, Holly Springs, Mississippi, 2008-2009; 1 folder(s) (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Clergy Correspondence – The Reverend Jim Trollinger, Jamestown United Methodist Church, and his wife, Sue, 1996-2015; 1 folder(s) (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence concerning the first appearances of Father Tim in "The Blowing Rocket", 1990-1991; 1 folder(s) (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Family Correspondence, 1991-2012; 1 folder(s) (Box 60, Folder 5)
      Correspondents include Phillip B. Bush II, Deanna Dickinson, Jennifer Gray, Sheridan Hill, Lisa Knaack, Gina Cloer Martin, Heather D. Rice, Taja Setzer, Cecil Wilson, and Lina White.
    - Family Correspondence, 2013-2016; 1 folder(s) (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Family Correspondence – Fannie Belle Bush Cloer (1893-1993), chiefly cards and letters from Jan Karon to her grandmother, 1986-1991; 1 folder(s) (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Family Correspondence – Fannie Belle Bush Cloer (1893-1993), chiefly cards and letters from Jan Karon to her grandmother, 1992-1993; 1 folder(s) (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Family Correspondence – David R. Craig, nephew of Jan Karon, and his family, 1994-2007; 1 folder(s) (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Family Correspondence – David R. Craig, nephew of Jan Karon, and his family, 2008-2011; 1 folder(s) (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Family Correspondence – David R. Craig, nephew of Jan Karon, and his family, 2012-2013; 1 folder(s) (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Family Correspondence – David R. Craig, nephew of Jan Karon, and his family, 2014-2016; 1 folder(s) (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Family Correspondence – Candace Rae Freeland, daughter of Jan Karon, 1988-1999; 1 folder(s) (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Family Correspondence – Candace Rae Freeland, daughter of Jan Karon, 2002-2004; 1 folder(s) (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Family Correspondence – Candace Rae Freeland, daughter of Jan Karon, 2005-2006; 1 folder(s) (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Family Correspondence – Candace Rae Freeland, daughter of Jan Karon, 2007-2009; 1 folder(s) (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Family Correspondence – Candace Rae Freeland, daughter of Jan Karon, 2010; 1 folder(s) (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Family Correspondence – Candace Rae Freeland, daughter of Jan Karon, 2011-2012; 1 folder(s) (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Family Correspondence – Candace Rae Freeland, daughter of Jan Karon, 2013; 1 folder(s) (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Family Correspondence – Candace Rae Freeland, daughter of Jan Karon, 2014; 1 folder(s) (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Family Correspondence – Candace Rae Freeland, daughter of Jan Karon, 2015-2016; 1 folder(s) (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Family Correspondence – Candace Rae Freeland, daughter of Jan Karon, undated; 1 folder(s) (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Family Correspondence – Brenda Furman, sister of Jan Karon, 1988-2007; 1 folder(s) (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Family Correspondence – Brenda Furman, sister of Jan Karon, 2008-2012; 1 folder(s) (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Family Correspondence – Brenda Furman, sister of Jan Karon, 2013-2016; 1 folder(s) (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Family Correspondence – Barry Setzer, brother of Jan Karon and his wife, Bonnie Setzer, 1988-2007; 1 folder(s) (Box 63, Folder 1)
      Includes a card featuring a watercolor of Esmont, October 30, 2003.
    - Family Correspondence – Barry Setzer, brother of Jan Karon and his wife, Bonnie Setzer, 2008-2010; 1 folder(s) (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Family Correspondence – Barry Setzer, brother of Jan Karon and his wife, Bonnie Setzer, 2011-2016; 1 folder(s) (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Family Correspondence – Wanda Setzer, mother of Jan Karon, 1975, 1988-2001; 1 folder(s) (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Family Correspondence – Wanda Setzer, mother of Jan Karon, 2002; 1 folder(s) (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Family Correspondence – Wanda Setzer, mother of Jan Karon, 2013-2016; 1 folder(s) (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Greeting Cards, 1987-1992; 1 folder(s) (Box 64, Folder 1)
      Note that some greeting card folders will also contain thank you cards and postcards from friends and family.
    - Greeting Cards - Birthday, 1988-1992; 1 folder(s) (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Greeting Cards, 1996; 1 folder(s) (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Greeting Cards, 1997; 1 folder(s) (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Greeting Cards - Birthday, 1997; 1 folder(s) (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Greeting Cards, many cards and notes concerning the death of Jan Karon’s dog, Rosie Potter, 1998; 1 folder(s) (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Greeting Cards, 1999; 1 folder(s) (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Greeting Cards, 2001; 1 folder(s) (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Greeting Cards - Birthday, 2001; 1 folder(s) (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Greeting Cards - Christmas, 2001; 1 folder(s) (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Greeting Cards, 2002; 1 folder(s) (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Greeting Cards - Birthday, 2002; 1 folder(s) (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Greeting Cards - Christmas, 2002; 1 folder(s) (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Greeting Cards - Christmas, 2002; 1 folder(s) (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Greeting Cards, 2003; 1 folder(s) (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Greeting Cards - Birthday, 2003; 1 folder(s) (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Greeting Cards - Christmas, 2003; 1 folder(s) (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Greeting Cards, 2004; 1 folder(s) (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Greeting Cards - Birthday, 2004; 1 folder(s) (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Greeting Cards, 2005; 1 folder(s) (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Greeting Cards - Birthday, 2005; 1 folder(s) (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Greeting Cards, 2006; 1 folder(s) (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Greeting Cards, 2007; 1 folder(s) (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Greeting Cards - Birthday, 2007; 1 folder(s) (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Greeting Cards - Birthday, 2007; 1 folder(s) (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Greeting Cards - Christmas, 2007; 1 folder(s) (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Greeting Cards, 2008; 1 folder(s) (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Greeting Cards - Birthday, 2008; 1 folder(s) (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Greeting Cards - Christmas, 2008; 1 folder(s) (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Greeting Cards, 2009; 1 folder(s) (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Greeting Cards - Birthday, 2009; 1 folder(s) (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Greeting Cards - Christmas, 2009; 1 folder(s) (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Greeting Cards, 2010 January-February; 1 folder(s) (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Greeting Cards, 2010 March-July; 1 folder(s) (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Greeting Cards, 2010 August-December; 1 folder(s) (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Greeting Cards - Birthday, 2010; 1 folder(s) (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Greeting Cards - Christmas, 2010; 1 folder(s) (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Greeting Cards, 2011 January-May; 1 folder(s) (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Greeting Cards, 2011 June-December; 1 folder(s) (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Greeting Cards - Christmas, 2011; 1 folder(s) (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Greeting Cards, 2012 January-February; 1 folder(s) (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Greeting Cards, 2012 March-December; 1 folder(s) (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Greeting Cards - Birthday, 2012; 1 folder(s) (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Greeting Cards, 2013 January-May; 1 folder(s) (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Greeting Cards, 2013 June-December; 1 folder(s) (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Greeting Cards - Birthday, 2013; 1 folder(s) (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Greeting Cards, 2014 January-March; 1 folder(s) (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Greeting Cards, 2014 April-December; 1 folder(s) (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Greeting Cards - Birthday, 2014; 1 folder(s) (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Greeting Cards - Christmas, 2014; 1 folder(s) (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Greeting Cards – Christmas, 2014; 1 folder(s) (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Greeting Cards – Christmas, 2014; 1 folder(s) (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Greeting Cards – Christmas, 2014; 1 folder(s) (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Greeting Cards, 2015; 1 folder(s) (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Greeting Cards – Birthday, 2015; 1 folder(s) (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Greeting Cards – Birthday celebration for Jan Karon given at the Inn at Little Washington by Donna and Albert Ernest, include mementoes of the occasion, 2015 April 15-16; 1 folder(s) (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Greeting Cards – Christmas, 2015; 1 folder(s) (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Greeting Cards – Christmas, 2015; 1 folder(s) (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Greeting Cards – Christmas, 2015; 1 folder(s) (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Greeting Cards, 2016; 1 folder(s) (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Greeting Cards - Birthday, 2016; 1 folder(s) (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Greeting Cards, undated; 1 folder(s) (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Invitations (9 folders), 1998-2014; Box 71; 9 folder(s)
    - Invitations, 2015-2016; 1 folder(s) (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1981-1989; 1 folder(s) (Box 72, Folder 2)
      One letter in particular, April 22, 1981, describes Jan Karon’s journey to the faith that is expressed throughout her books and personal appearances.
    - Personal Correspondence (6 folders), 1990-2000; Box 72; 6 folder(s)
    - Personal Correspondence (8 folders), 2001-2006; Box 73; 8 folder(s)
    - Personal Correspondence (7 folders), 2007-2010 July; Box 74; 7 folder(s)
    - Personal Correspondence (8 folders), 2010 August-2013 December; Box 75; 8 folder(s)
    - Personal Correspondence (7 folders), 2014 January-2016 March; Box 76; 7 folder(s)
    - Personal Correspondence – Ron Adair, illustrator, 2005; 1 folder(s) (Box 77, Folder 1)
      Includes Mitford sketches and two prints of Presidents Ronald Reagan (2002) and George W. Bush by Adair (2003).
    - Personal Correspondence – Everett Barrineau, former Penguin sales representative who actively promoted Karon’s books, 1989-2015; 1 folder(s) (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Personal Correspondence – Arlette and Patrick de Barros, Esmont neighbors, 2004-2016; 1 folder(s) (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Personal Correspondence – Nancy Lou Beard, Blowing Rock neighbor, 1999-2002; 1 folder(s) (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Personal Correspondence – Paula and Jerome Beazley, Esmont neighbors, 2000-2001; 1 folder(s) (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Personal Correspondence – Nancy Adams Briggs (1959- ), former personal assistant to Jan Karon, hired in 2001, 2001-2005; 1 folder(s) (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Personal Correspondence – Nancy Adams Briggs (1959- ), former personal assistant to Jan Karon, hired in 2001, 2006-2009; 1 folder(s) (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Personal Correspondence – Nancy Adams Briggs (1959- ), former personal assistant to Jan Karon, hired in 2001, 2010-2015; 1 folder(s) (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Personal Correspondence – Barbara Bush (1925- ), former first lady, 1998-2002; 1 folder(s) (Box 77, Folder 9)
      Existence and Location of Originals
      All original Barbara Bush letters have been transferred to the vault but copies have been retained in the Jan Karon papers.
    - Personal Correspondence – Barbara Bush (1925- ), former first lady, 2003-2014; 1 folder(s) (Box 77, Folder 10)
      All original Barbara Bush letters have been tranferred to the vault but copies have been kept in the Jan Karon papers.
    - Personal Correspondence – President George W. Bush (1946- ) and Laura Bush (1946- ), former first lady, 2000-2002; 1 folder(s) (Box 77, Folder 11)
      All original Laura Bush letters have been transferred to the vault but copies have been retained in the Jan Karon papers.
    - Personal Correspondence – Bessie Carter, 2000-2006; 1 folder(s) (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Personal Correspondence – Lee Stuart Cochran (1924- ), 2001-2016; 1 folder(s) (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Personal Correspondence – Charles W. Colson (1931-2012), 2000-2005; 1 folder(s) (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Personal Correspondence – Charlotte Dark, 2005-2013; 1 folder(s) (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Personal Correspondence – Charlotte Dark, 2014-2016; 1 folder(s) (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Personal Correspondence – Albert and Donna Ernest, 2002-2015; 1 folder(s) (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Personal Correspondence – Hunter Floyd, 1997-2005; 1 folder(s) (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Personal Correspondence – Eddie Glover, 1989-1994; 1 folder(s) (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - Personal Correspondence – Ruth Bell Graham (1920-2007) and Billy Graham (1918- ) family, 1995-2002; 1 folder(s) (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Personal Correspondence – Ruth Bell Graham (1920-2007) and Billy Graham (1918- ) family, 2003-2016; 1 folder(s) (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Personal Correspondence – Ruth Bell Graham (1920-2007) and Billy Graham (1918- ) family - Commemorative publications honoring Ruth Bell Graham, 1 folder(s) (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Personal Correspondence – Andrew D. Hart and Margaret Hart, Esmont neighbors, 2000-2016; 1 folder(s) (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Personal Correspondence – Dorothy C. Helms, wife of former Senator Jesse Helms (1919-2015), 1999-2003; 1 folder(s) (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Personal Correspondence – Carol Hill, former assistant to Jan Karon, 2004-2005; 1 folder(s) (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - Personal Correspondence – James Davison Hunter (1955- ), University of Virginia professor, 2002-2008; 1 folder(s) (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Personal Correspondence – Emyl Jenkins (1941-2010), antiques appraiser and author, 1996-2009; 1 folder(s) (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - Personal Correspondence - Dan Jordan, former head of the Thomas Jefferson Foundation (Monticello) and his wife, and Lou Jordan, who is an artist, 2000-2001; 1 folder(s) (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - Personal Correspondence - Dan Jordan, former head of the Thomas Jefferson Foundation (Monticello) and his wife, and Lou Jordan, who is an artist, 2002-2003; 1 folder(s) (Box 79, Folder 10)